CONTACTS



Syria, Damscuse



Ghfranalheshan5@gmail.com



+963935576965

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ghfran-al-heshan-b0196921b

EDUCATION

 Damascus University _ Information Technology Engineering

Under-graduate Student at fourth year 2019 -now

COURSES

- Basics of php language 2021
- Web development creative group -2021
- Laravel 8 PHP framework –
 Udemy-2022
- Git and GitHub professional course -2022

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication skills
- Working in a team
- Work under pressure
- Adaptability
- Problem solving

HARD SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Git
- Restfull api
- Database management
- Eloquent ORM
- Oop
- Html,Css

LANGUAGES

English

Ghfran AL heshan

Laravel developer

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I study at the Faculty of Informatics Engineering, I have more than two years of experience in developing applications and web sites using 'Laravel framework 'and my sql databases, I worked alone, and I worked as part of a team, I look forward to more experiences in this field

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ecommerce

11/2021 - 01/2022

A simple android application developed by Laravel and Fluttter frameworks with my Sql databases.

The main goal is market products online

There are two types of users:

- The buyer
- The seller

Basic services provided by the application:

- Register an account and management it
- Add/delete/modify products
- Presentation of products
- Possibility of interaction(add like or comments) with products
- Products evaluation
- Search and classification

Wherehousemanagement system(WMS): 03/2022 - 08/2022

I participated in the development of a warehouse management system application as a backend developer ,it's an android application developed by Laravel and Fluttter frameworks with my Sql databases.

The main goal is to manage the operations that occur within big or intermediate warehouses $\boldsymbol{.}$

There five types of users:

- Big boss
- Accountant
- Seller
- Supplier

Basic services provided by the application:

- Register a manager accountant
- Managing employee accounts(Seller Supplier ,Supervisor, accountant)
- Managing import and supply requests
- Add, view, modify and browse (products, categories, Department)
- Managing trucks and workers.
- Billing system
- Reports system
- Reservation system
 Non_ functional requirements:
- Permissions management
- Send a verification code via email

Money transfer system To 'Sultan Trading company' freelance 10/2022- 02/2023

I participated in the development money transfer system as a backend developer ,it's a website developed by Laravel and javascript ,with my sql databases.

There are two types of users:

- Main office
- Branch offices

Basic services provided by the website:

- Remittance management
- Branch office accounts management
- Managing financial funds
- Active or deactivate the money exchange feature
- Show earning